opsgenie.com 2017-08-23

# OpsGenie | Privacy Policy

At OpsGenie we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to your use of the OpsGenie applications on all platforms (the "Application" or "Applications"), the related services we provide ("OpsGenie Services") and the Site. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service ("TOS") found at <https://www.opsgenie.com/tos>.

This Policy covers the Applications, the OpsGenie Services and the Site. It does not cover any applications, Web sites, products or services that we do not control or own. By using any Application, the OpsGenie Services or the Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter this Policy at any time. You can find the most recent version of this Policy at <https://www.opsgenie.com/privacy>, with the date of last modification noted above. Such modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof on the Site. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you access or use an Application, the OpsGenie Services or the Site to check if this Policy has been updated. You must review this Policy on a regular basis to keep yourself apprised of any changes. If you do not agree to any modifications to this Policy, your sole recourse is to immediately stop all use of all Applications, the OpsGenie Services and the Site. Your continued use of any Application, the OpsGenie Services or the Site following the posting of any modifications to this Policy will constitute your acceptance of the revised Policy. Should you have any questions regarding this Policy, please contact us at the contact information listed at the end of this Policy. Please note that none of our employees or agents has the authority to vary any of our Policies. 

### What kind of information we collect

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience.

We collect information about your use of an Application, the OpsGenie Services and/or the Site and includes, without limitation, connection and service-related data submitted to us through your use of an Application, the OpsGenie Services or the Site. Session and Usage Data includes information relating to the connection request, server communication and data sharing, including network measurements, quality of service, and date, time and location of the OpsGenie.

When you interact with us or use an Application, the OpsGenie Services or our Site, our systems may automatically collect your unique User Device number, the IP address, type of browser or operating system you use, and the dates and times of your use

We also collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, device name, phone number or email address. Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, email, or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: [support@opsgenie.com](mailto:support@opsgenie.com)

### What we do with the information

We do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies for marketing purposes. We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting.

In order to serve you, we may share your personal and anonymous information with other companies, including vendors and contractors. Their use of information is limited to these purposes, and subject to agreements that require them to keep the information confidential. Our vendors provide assurance that they take reasonable steps to safeguard the data they hold on our behalf, although data security cannot be guaranteed.

Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

This privacy policy was last updated on June 19, 2017. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
